[
    {
        "question": "1. A solid hemisphere has a radius of 7 cm. Find the total surface area", 
        "optionA": "400 cm2", 
        "optionB": "462 cm2", 
        "optionC": "66 cm2",
        "optionD": "308 cm2",
        "answer": "462 cm2"
    },
    {
        "question": "2. Solve 52(x-1) x 5(x-1) = 0.04", 
        "optionA": "1/3", 
        "optionB": "1/6", 
        "optionC": "-1/5",
        "optionD": "-1/3",
        "answer": "1/3" 
    },
    {
        "question": "3. If the 2nd and 5th terms of a G.P are 6 and 48 respectively, find the sum of the first for term",
        "optionA": "-45",
        "optionB": "-15",
        "optionC": "15",
        "optionD": "45",
        "answer": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. The length of an exercise book is given as 20cm correct to the nearest centimeter. In which of the following ranges of possible measurement does the actual length lie",
        "optionA": "19.5 - 20.4cm",
        "optionB": "19.1 - 20.9cm",
        "optionC": "19.95 - 20.05cm",
        "optionD": "19 - 21cm",
        "answer": "19.5 - 20.4cm"
    },
    {
        "question": "5. Solve the equation (x - 2) (x - 3) = 12",
        "optionA": "2, 3",
        "optionB": "3, 6",
        "optionC": "-1, 6",
        "optionD": "1, -6",
        "answer": "-1, 6"
    },
    {
        "question": "6. Find all real numbers x which satisfy the inequality 1/3(x + 1) - 1 > 1/5(x + 4)",
        "optionA": "x < 11",
        "optionB": "x < -1",
        "optionC": "x > 6",
        "optionD": "x > 11",
        "answer": "x > 11"
    },
    {
        "question": "7. If M represents the median and D the mode of the measurements 5, 9, 3, 5, 7, 5, 8 then (M, D) is",
        "optionA": "(6, 5)",
        "optionB": " (5, 5)",
        "optionC": "(5, 8)",
        "optionD": "(7, 5)",
        "answer": " (5, 5)"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. A rectangular picture 6cm by 8cm is enclosed by a frame 1/2cm wide. Calculate the area of the frame",
        "optionA": "15sq.cm",
        "optionB": "13sq.cm",
        "optionC": "16sq.cm",
        "optionD": "17sq.cm",
        "answer": "15sq.cm"
    },
    {
        "question": "9. Five years ago, a father was 3 times as old as his son, now their combined ages amount to 110years. thus, the present age of the father is",
        "optionA": "75 years",
        "optionB": "105 years",
        "optionC": "80 years",
        "optionD": "60 years",
        "answer": "80 years"
    },
    {
        "question": "10. If x2 + kx + 16/9 is a perfect square, find the value of k",
        "optionA": "8/3",
        "optionB": "7/3",
        "optionC": "5/3",
        "optionD": "2/3",
        "answer": "8/3"
    }
]